AgentPay Firewall turns autonomous agent payments into policy-controlled infrastructure.
AI agents can call paid APIs, but they should not spend from a wallet without rules, budgets, and audit trails.
The user defines the mandate: request cap, daily budget, approved services, network, asset, risk score, and human approval threshold.
First, the agent calls a paid wallet-risk API. The server returns an HTTP 402 challenge with PAYMENT-REQUIRED.
The firewall checks every gate. This request passes, so it signs, retries, and receives PAYMENT-RESPONSE.
Now the unsafe path. A costly non-allowlisted crawl gets the same challenge, but policy fails before signing.
A third request is allowed, but crosses the human approval threshold. The wallet pauses instead of silently spending.
For the production path, the buyer key stays inside OKX Wallet. The app asks OKX to sign x402 typed data with eth_signTypedData_v4.
We reproduced that path on Base Sepolia. The facilitator settled 0.001 USDC and returned an official x402 receipt with an explorer transaction.
So the project is not just another agent wallet. It is the control layer that decides when autonomous payments are safe to execute.